Hello friends, in today's video we will talk
about ICICI Bank, which has
launched the digital platform of the bank. In this, you can avail 500 types of
services sitting at home by messaging Ram Swaroop
or Kapoor, if there is a requirement for this, you
can apply for it sitting at home, there is
no need to go to the bank. So,
friends, in this, the seal of the bank, which they
told through this conference,
which types of facilities are there in it, which
500 types of digital services have been
provided to the customer, so you
can use them like this, which
stocks have been given, service tax,
loan from Indore, account opened, this type of
Jose Statham, I will explain in detail in this video
and you watch this video and
understand the track, which step, where and
how it will work.
First of all, friends, in this,
if you want to open any Edifice type account, then
you can easily get it done through the system sitting at home.
Section 2 is
payment track, if you have to make any payment
like merchant  This type of settlement customer will be available to
you and you
can easily make a mistake in this
through chemistry. The third number comes to
Dastak in this, if you need a loan from any side
like Equity Loan, Home Loan, Finance Loan,
Digital Goods Ticket Record, first of all if you
add such accounts then you will easily
get some facilities in it sitting at home, you do not need to go to the bank,
investment in this is one step in which the customer
needs state service, FD will be hard yoga,
size pace and if you
want any similar loan then you
can manage it comfortably sitting at home
through this investment track and next
comes Cars Tag,
in this if you want to buy a health two wheeler or a
car etc. or any step of home loan etc. then it comes
in the middle tag, in this
you can easily apply for it sitting at home,
if you have a good trick,
any puri, you have to do it on the back, then you can
easily go here and cook it, then
you do not need to go to the bank, so
friends, such a bank has taken a very good initiative  It has been done
for the customers in digital service
so that the customers do not have to
go to the bank, they do not have to worry about how they will be
able to manage their account, how they will be able to do the bank
work sitting at home, so
friends, these were some tests, Manju Manju
told that the way to clean, if you should have complete
information, you will
go to the bank website, you will get the details, you can
download it from there and
see it easily, so friends, these are four-five types
of services, before that
start your WhatsApp banking, check the
balance through WhatsApp, how
can you take services, friends, there
will be tax as per this,
I told you that whatever service of ₹500 is there,
you should see it,
any stuck work can be easily taken from home, so
friends,
if you like this ICICI Bank license pack video, then
like and share it and you will keep
getting similar sexy videos on my channel, till then
please subscribe to my channel,
thank you friends, so